https://www.missiondc.org/privacy-policy/

Manage My Account
Need Help?
Home > Privacy Policy
Central Union Mission is committed to protecting your privacy and your personal information provided via the Site.
Information we collect
We collect information from offline donors as well as the following visitors on our website:
From those interested in requesting information or materials from Central Union Mission
From those who make a purchase
From those who donate
How we use this information
Central Union Mission uses your information to provide you with service. In the case of donations, we use your information to complete a transaction. Credit card numbers are used only for donation or payment processing and are not retained for any other purpose. Credit card numbers are only kept in our files until the transaction is completed.
We do not share personal information
Central Union Mission never sells, rents, leases or exchanges the information obtained from donors with other organizations. We assure you the identity of all who contact us through this website will be kept confidential. Use of personal information will be limited to the internal purposes of Central Union Mission. We will not send donor mailings on behalf of other organizations.
Use of Cookies
Central Union Mission uses cookies to enhance the website and improve user experiences online. The cookies never include personal information such as name, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. We have no way of collecting such information from the cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major websites use them to provide useful features for their customers. Visitors can also accept or reject cookies. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your browser to reject cookies.
Opt-Out Instructions
If you do not want to receive future emails from us, please let us know by sending us an email to info@missiondc.org. If you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending us an email to info@missiondc.org. Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding support and services and/or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending us an email at info@missiondc.org. Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list.
Central Union Mission uses Internet Encryption Software, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. Credit card information you enter is encrypted at your browser, sent over the public Internet in encrypted form, then decrypted at our server. Once we receive your credit card information, it is accessible only to a small number of trusted Central Union Mission’s staff who have been specially trained in processing this information.
Your Gift of $115 helps 60 people
$35
$50
$100
$250
$500
Donate Now
STAY INFORMED
Let's connect. Subscribe to get our latest news.
Name*
Email*
CAPTCHA
Home
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Financials
Contact Us
Press
Donate Now
Central Union Mission
65 Massachusetts Avenue, NW
Washington DC 20001
(202) 745-7118
© 2020 Central Union Mission. A 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization. All donations are tax deductible to the full extent of the law. All Rights Reserved.
Your Impact
Impact Stats
Stories of Change
Mission Memories
Get Involved
Volunteer
Events
Follow Us On
of the Year – 2020
Passport Auto Group donates both time and money to worthy community organizations to thank them for their help in making our community a better place to work and live.
Donate Now Follow Us On
Central Union Mission
65 Massachusetts Avenue, NW
Washington DC 20001
(202) 745-7118
© 2020 Central Union Mission. A 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization. All donations are tax deductible to the full extent of the law. All Rights Reserved.
Business Sponsor
of the Year – 2020
Passport Auto Group donates both time and money to worthy community organizations to thank them for their help in making our community a better place to work and live.
